

# Skills

#### Personal

I don't mind working under pressure, always better to be too busy than bored. I enjoy being engaged right from the inception of new projects and also taking time to improve existing processes and frameworks.

#### **Technical**

Have built relationships and led initiatives across other teams to drive business goals. Experienced with high scale data migration including across regions. Also have a "fast mode" - can spin up small / medium scale webapps in no time at all.

#### Development

Highly competent in Java, AWS, Terraform, TypeScript and Vue.js

# Relevant Experience

## Canva • Senior Backend Engineer • October 2021 - Current

- Managed all landing pages on canva.com and canva.cn. On average these pages receive 30 million requests per day.
- Led projects to enable experimentation and fallback mechanisms in the China region.
- Worked on CMS and page rendering backend features in *Typescript* and *Java*, including syncing millions of rows of data between DynamoDB and Postgres databases.
- Led the initiative to let content managers configure page URLs, increasing TTM and decreasing load on engineering teams.

### Two Bulls • Full-Stack Engineer • January 2020 - October 2021

- Built numerous web applications with Vue frontend and Serverless / Typescript backend, including deployment using AWS services.
- Projects include: the <u>KidsDoc telehealth platform</u>, <u>TheOneTwo</u> lingerie shopfront, the <u>Victorian COVID</u> border permits service (reached #3 on the app store!) and the <u>Release.Me</u> land sales platform.

#### Unico • Associate Developer • January 2019 - January 2020

- Performed database migrations / ETL for large telecommunications vendors
- Wrote Java / Spring applications to move databases of up to 20 million records to the MATRIXX inmemory database
- Gained experience in data-intensive systems and concurrency, plus conducting thorough testing to secure personal data and reverse engineer older systems.

#### Monash University Immersive Analytics Team • July 2017 - January 2020

• Developed a highly performant web application for 2D and 3D visualisation of protein complexes and cross-link mass spectrometry data using *Three.js* and *WebGL* 

#### Inquire to find out more...

- UAVs
- Cluster computing competitions
- Side projects

## Education



Bachelor of Computer Science Monash University Clayton, VIC, Australia